PERPETUAL INCOME 365 PRIVACY POLICY AND TERMS OF SERVICE

If you continue to browse and use this website, you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy govern our relationship with you in relation to this website.

If you disagree with any part of these terms and conditions, please do not use our website.

The terms 'us' or 'we' refers to the owner of the website.

The term 'you' refers to the user or viewer of our website.

The use of this website is subject to the following terms of use:

The content of the pages of this website is for your general information and use only.It is subject to change without notice.

Neither we nor any third parties provide any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness or suitability of the information and materials found or offered on this website for any particular purpose.

You acknowledge that such information and materials may contain inaccuracies or errors and we expressly exclude liability for any such inaccuracies or errors to the fullest extent permitted by law.

Your use of any information or materials on this website is entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable.

It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any products, services or information available through this website meet your specific requirements.

This website contains material which is owned by or licensed to us.

This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions.

All trademarks reproduced in this website, which are not the property of, or licensed to the operator, are acknowledged on the website.

Unauthorized use of this website may give rise to a claim for damages and/or be a criminal offense.

From time to time, this website may also include links to other websites.

These links are provided for your convenience to provide further information.

They do not signify that we endorse the website(s).

We have no responsibility for the content of the linked website(s).

Privacy Policy and Earning Disclaimer

WE UNDERSTAND THAT PRIVACY ONLINE IS IMPORTANT TO USERS OF OUR SITE, ESPECIALLY WHEN CONDUCTING BUSINESS. THIS STATEMENT GOVERNS OUR PRIVACY POLICIES WITH RESPECT TO THOSE USERS OF THE SITE ("VISITORS") WHO VISIT WITHOUT TRANSACTING BUSINESS AND VISITORS WHO REGISTER TO TRANSACT BUSINESS ON THE SITE AND MAKE USE OF THE VARIOUS SERVICES OFFERED BY WEBSITE SALES FUNNELS COLLECTIVELY, ("SERVICES") ("AUTHORIZED CUSTOMERS").

PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION REFERS TO ANY INFORMATION THAT IDENTIFIES OR CAN BE USED TO IDENTIFY, CONTACT, OR LOCATE THE PERSON TO WHOM SUCH INFORMATION PERTAINS, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, NAME, ADDRESS, PHONE NUMBER, FAX NUMBER, EMAIL ADDRESS, FINANCIAL PROFILES, SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER, AND CREDIT CARD INFORMATION.

PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION DOES NOT INCLUDE INFORMATION THAT IS COLLECTED ANONYMOUSLY (THAT IS, WITHOUT IDENTIFICATION OF THE INDIVIDUAL USER) OR DEMOGRAPHIC INFORMATION NOT CONNECTED TO AN IDENTIFIED INDIVIDUAL. WHAT PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION IS COLLECTED.

WE MAY COLLECT BASIC USER PROFILE INFORMATION FROM ALL OF OUR VISITORS. WE COLLECT THE FOLLOWING ADDITIONAL INFORMATION FROM OUR AUTHORIZED CUSTOMERS:

THE NAMES, ADDRESSES, PHONE NUMBERS AND EMAIL ADDRESSES OF AUTHORIZED CUSTOMERS, THE NATURE AND SIZE OF THE BUSINESS, AND THE NATURE AND SIZE OF THE ADVERTISING INVENTORY THAT THE AUTHORIZED CUSTOMER INTENDS TO PURCHASE OR SELL. WHAT ORGANIZATIONS ARE COLLECTING THE INFORMATION IN ADDITION TO OUR DIRECT COLLECTION OF INFORMATION, OUR THIRD PARTY SERVICE VENDORS (SUCH AS CREDIT CARD COMPANIES, CLEARINGHOUSES, AND BANKS) WHO MAY PROVIDE SUCH SERVICES AS CREDIT, INSURANCE, AND ESCROW SERVICES MAY COLLECT THIS INFORMATION FROM OUR VISITORS AND AUTHORIZED CUSTOMERS. WE DO NOT CONTROL HOW THESE THIRD PARTIES USE SUCH INFORMATION, BUT WE DO ASK THEM TO DISCLOSE HOW THEY USE PERSONAL INFORMATION PROVIDED TO THEM FROM VISITORS AND AUTHORIZED CUSTOMERS. SOME OF THESE THIRD PARTIES MAY BE INTERMEDIARIES THAT ACT SOLELY AS LINKS IN THE DISTRIBUTION CHAIN AND DO NOT STORE, RETAIN, OR USE THE INFORMATION GIVEN TO THEM.

HOW DOES THE SITE USE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION:

WE USE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION TO CUSTOMIZE THE SITE, TO MAKE APPROPRIATE SERVICE OFFERINGS, AND TO FULFILL BUYING AND SELLING REQUESTS ON THE SITE. WE MAY EMAIL VISITORS AND AUTHORIZED CUSTOMERS ABOUT RESEARCH OR PURCHASE AND SELLING OPPORTUNITIES ON THE SITE OR INFORMATION RELATED TO THE SUBJECT MATTER OF THE SITE.

WE MAY ALSO USE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION TO CONTACT VISITORS AND AUTHORIZED CUSTOMERS IN RESPONSE TO SPECIFIC INQUIRIES, OR TO PROVIDE REQUESTED INFORMATION.

WITH WHOM MAY THE INFORMATION BE SHARED:

PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION ABOUT AUTHORIZED CUSTOMERS MAY BE SHARED WITH OTHER AUTHORIZED CUSTOMERS WHO WISH TO EVALUATE POTENTIAL TRANSACTIONS WITH OTHER AUTHORIZED CUSTOMERS.  WE MAY SHARE AGGREGATED INFORMATION ABOUT OUR VISITORS, INCLUDING THE DEMOGRAPHICS OF OUR VISITORS AND AUTHORIZED CUSTOMERS, WITH OUR AFFILIATED AGENCIES AND THIRD-PARTY VENDORS. WE ALSO OFFER THE OPPORTUNITY TO "OPT-OUT" OF RECEIVING INFORMATION OR BEING CONTACTED BY US OR BY ANY AGENCY ACTING ON OUR BEHALF.

HOW IS PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION STORED:

PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT IS SECURELY STORED AND IS NOT ACCESSIBLE TO THIRD PARTIES OR EMPLOYEES EXCEPT FOR USE AS INDICATED ABOVE.  WHAT CHOICES ARE AVAILABLE TO VISITORS REGARDING COLLECTION, USE AND DISTRIBUTION OF THE INFORMATION VISITORS AND AUTHORIZED CUSTOMERS MAY OPT OUT OF RECEIVING UNSOLICITED INFORMATION FROM OR BEING CONTACTED BY US AND/OR OUR VENDORS AND AFFILIATED AGENCIES BY RESPONDING TO EMAILS AS INSTRUCTED.

COOKIES USED ON THE SITE COOKIES ARE USED FOR A VARIETY OF REASONS. WE USE COOKIES TO OBTAIN INFORMATION ABOUT THE PREFERENCES OF OUR VISITORS AND THE SERVICES THEY SELECT.  WE ALSO USE COOKIES FOR SECURITY PURPOSES TO PROTECT OUR AUTHORIZED CUSTOMERS. FOR EXAMPLE, IF AN AUTHORIZED CUSTOMER IS LOGGED ON AND THE SITE IS UNUSED FOR MORE THAN 10 MINUTES, WE WILL AUTOMATICALLY LOG THE AUTHORIZED CUSTOMER OFF.

HOW DO WE USE LOGIN INFORMATION:

WE USE LOGIN INFORMATION, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IP ADDRESSES, IPS, AND BROWSER TYPES, TO ANALYZE TRENDS, ADMINISTER THE SITE, TRACK A USER'S MOVEMENT AND USE, AND GATHER BROAD DEMOGRAPHIC INFORMATION.  WHAT PARTNERS OR SERVICE PROVIDERS HAVE ACCESS TO PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION FROM VISITORS AND/OR AUTHORIZED CUSTOMERS ON THE SITE WE HAVE ENTERED INTO AND WILL CONTINUE TO ENTER INTO PARTNERSHIPS AND OTHER AFFILIATIONS WITH A NUMBER OF VENDORS.  SUCH VENDORS MAY HAVE ACCESS TO CERTAIN PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION ON A NEED TO KNOW BASIS FOR EVALUATING AUTHORIZED CUSTOMERS FOR SERVICE ELIGIBILITY.

OUR PRIVACY POLICY DOES NOT COVER THEIR COLLECTION OR USE OF THIS INFORMATION. DISCLOSURE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION TO COMPLY WITH LAW.  WE WILL DISCLOSE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION IN ORDER TO COMPLY WITH A COURT ORDER OR SUBPOENA OR A REQUEST FROM A LAW ENFORCEMENT AGENCY TO RELEASE INFORMATION. WE WILL ALSO DISCLOSE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION WHEN REASONABLY NECESSARY TO PROTECT THE SAFETY OF OUR VISITORS AND AUTHORIZED CUSTOMERS.  

HOW DOES THE SITE KEEP PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION SECURE:

ALL OF OUR EMPLOYEES ARE FAMILIAR WITH OUR SECURITY POLICY AND PRACTICES. THE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION OF OUR VISITORS AND AUTHORIZED CUSTOMERS IS ONLY ACCESSIBLE TO A LIMITED NUMBER OF QUALIFIED EMPLOYEES WHO ARE GIVEN A PASSWORD IN ORDER TO GAIN ACCESS TO THE INFORMATION.  WE AUDIT OUR SECURITY SYSTEMS AND PROCESSES ON A REGULAR BASIS. SENSITIVE INFORMATION, SUCH AS CREDIT CARD NUMBERS OR SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBERS, IS PROTECTED BY ENCRYPTION PROTOCOLS, IN PLACE TO PROTECT INFORMATION SENT OVER THE INTERNET. WHILE WE TAKE COMMERCIALLY REASONABLE MEASURES TO MAINTAIN A SECURE SITE, ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS AND DATABASES ARE SUBJECT TO ERRORS, TAMPERING AND BREAK-INS, AND WE CANNOT GUARANTEE OR WARRANT THAT SUCH EVENTS WILL NOT TAKE PLACE AND WE WILL NOT BE LIABLE TO VISITORS OR AUTHORIZED CUSTOMERS FOR ANY SUCH OCCURRENCES.  

HOW CAN VISITORS CORRECT ANY INACCURACIES IN PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION VISITORS AND AUTHORIZED CUSTOMERS MAY CONTACT US TO UPDATE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION ABOUT THEM OR TO CORRECT ANY INACCURACIES BY CONTACTING US FROM THE ABOUT US PAGE CAN A VISITOR DELETE OR DEACTIVATE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THE SITE WE PROVIDE VISITORS AND AUTHORIZED CUSTOMERS WITH A MECHANISM TO DELETE/DEACTIVATE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION FROM THE SITE'S DATABASE BY EMAIL.  HOWEVER, BECAUSE OF BACKUPS AND RECORDS OF DELETIONS, IT MAY BE IMPOSSIBLE TO DELETE A VISITOR'S ENTRY WITHOUT RETAINING SOME RESIDUAL INFORMATION. AN INDIVIDUAL WHO REQUESTS TO HAVE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION DEACTIVATED WILL HAVE THIS INFORMATION FUNCTIONALLY DELETED, AND WE WILL NOT SELL, TRANSFER, OR USE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION RELATING TO THAT INDIVIDUAL IN ANY WAY MOVING FORWARD.

WHAT HAPPENS IF THE PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES:

WE WILL LET OUR VISITORS AND AUTHORIZED CUSTOMERS KNOW ABOUT CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY BY POSTING SUCH CHANGES ON THE SITE.  HOWEVER, IF WE ARE CHANGING OUR PRIVACY POLICY IN A MANNER THAT MIGHT CAUSE DISCLOSURE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION THAT A VISITOR OR AUTHORIZED CUSTOMER HAS PREVIOUSLY REQUESTED NOT BE DISCLOSED, WE WILL CONTACT SUCH VISITOR OR AUTHORIZED CUSTOMER TO ALLOW SUCH VISITOR OR AUTHORIZED CUSTOMER TO PREVENT SUCH DISCLOSURE LINKS.  THIS WEB SITE CONTAINS LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES. PLEASE NOTE THAT WHEN YOU CLICK ON ONE OF THESE LINKS, YOU ARE MOVING TO ANOTHER WEB SITE. WE ENCOURAGE YOU TO READ THE PRIVACY STATEMENTS OF THESE LINKED SITES AS THEIR PRIVACY POLICIES MAY DIFFER FROM OURS.

ANY EARNINGS OR INCOME STATEMENTS, OR EARNINGS OR INCOME EXAMPLES, ARE NOT TYPICAL AND, AS SUCH, THERE IS NO ASSURANCE YOU'LL DO AS WELL.  IF YOU RELY UPON THE FIGURES DISPLAYED ON THIS WEBSITE, YOU MUST ACCEPT THE RISK OF NOT DOING AS WELL. WHERE SPECIFIC INCOME FIGURES ARE USED AND ATTRIBUTED TO AN INDIVIDUAL OR BUSINESS, THOSE PERSONS OR BUSINESSES HAVE EARNED THAT AMOUNT.  THERE IS NO ASSURANCE YOU'LL DO AS WELL. IF YOU RELY UPON OUR FIGURES; YOU MUST ACCEPT THE RISK OF NOT DOING AS WELL. ANY AND ALL CLAIMS OR REPRESENTATIONS, AS TO INCOME EARNINGS ON THIS WEB SITE, ARE NOT TO BE CONSIDERED AS AVERAGE EARNINGS.  TESTIMONIALS ARE NOT REPRESENTATIVE. THERE CAN BE NO ASSURANCE THAT ANY PRIOR SUCCESSES, OR PAST RESULTS, AS TO INCOME EARNINGS, CAN BE USED AS AN INDICATION OF YOUR FUTURE SUCCESS OR RESULTS. MONETARY AND INCOME RESULTS ARE BASED ON MANY FACTORS.  WE HAVE NO WAY OF KNOWING HOW WELL YOU WILL DO, AS WE DO NOT KNOW YOU, YOUR BACKGROUND, YOUR WORK ETHIC, OR YOUR BUSINESS SKILLS OR PRACTICES. THEREFORE WE DO NOT GUARANTEE OR IMPLY THAT YOU WILL WIN ANY INCENTIVES OR PRIZES THAT MAY BE OFFERED, GET RICH, THAT YOU WILL DO AS WELL, OR MAKE ANY MONEY AT ALL. THERE IS NO ASSURANCE YOU'LL DO AS WELL.

IF YOU RELY UPON OUR FIGURES; YOU MUST ACCEPT THE RISK OF NOT DOING AS WELL. INTERNET BUSINESSES AND EARNINGS DERIVED THEREFROM, HAVE UNKNOWN RISKS INVOLVED, AND ARE NOT SUITABLE FOR EVERYONE. MAKING DECISIONS BASED ON ANY INFORMATION PRESENTED IN OUR PRODUCTS, SERVICES, OR WEBSITE SHOULD BE DONE ONLY WITH THE KNOWLEDGE THAT YOU COULD EXPERIENCE SIGNIFICANT LOSSES, OR MAKE NO MONEY AT ALL.

ALL PRODUCTS AND SERVICES BY OUR COMPANY ARE FOR EDUCATIONAL AND INFORMATIONAL PURPOSES ONLY. USE CAUTION AND SEEK THE ADVICE OF QUALIFIED PROFESSIONALS. CHECK WITH YOUR ACCOUNTANT, LAWYER OR PROFESSIONAL ADVISOR, BEFORE ACTING ON THIS OR ANY INFORMATION.

USERS OF OUR PRODUCTS, SERVICES, AND WEB SITE ARE ADVISED TO DO THEIR OWN DUE DILIGENCE WHEN IT COMES TO MAKING BUSINESS DECISIONS AND ALL INFORMATION, PRODUCTS, AND SERVICES THAT HAVE BEEN PROVIDED SHOULD BE INDEPENDENTLY VERIFIED BY YOUR OWN QUALIFIED PROFESSIONALS. OUR INFORMATION, PRODUCTS, AND SERVICES ON THIS WEB SITE SHOULD BE CAREFULLY CONSIDERED AND EVALUATED, BEFORE REACHING A BUSINESS DECISION, ON WHETHER TO RELY ON THEM. ALL DISCLOSURES AND DISCLAIMERS MADE HEREIN OR ON OUR SITE, APPLY EQUALLY TO ANY OFFERS, PRIZES, OR INCENTIVES, THAT MAY BE MADE BY OUR COMPANY.

YOU AGREE THAT OUR COMPANY IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE SUCCESS OR FAILURE OF YOUR BUSINESS DECISIONS RELATING TO ANY INFORMATION PRESENTED BY OUR COMPANY, OR OUR COMPANY PRODUCTS OR SERVICES.

Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select "Remember Me", your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

Need additional help? [Click Here!](https://www.perpetualincome365.site/2.0/help/)
